<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FruitGame</string>
    <string name="orange_en">Orange (Scientific name: Citrus sinensis English: orange), is a Citrus plant orange tree fruit of rutaceae, also known as yellow fruit, Citrus, golden ring, liuding.
Orange tree is a small tree. The fruit can be peeled and eaten fresh with its flesh, which can be used as a condiment or addition to other foods</string>
    <string name="orange_cn">橙子（学名：Citrus sinensis 英语：orange），是芸香科柑橘属植物橙树的果实，亦称为黄果、柑子、金环、柳丁。橙树属小乔木。果实可以剥皮鲜食其果肉，果肉可以用作其他食物的调料或附加物</string>
    <string name="apple_en">Apple (Malus pumila Mill.) : deciduous trees, usually up to 15 meters tall, but cultivated trees are usually only about 3-5 meters tall. The trunk is grayish-brown and the bark is somewhat abscissive. Apple blossom season is based on the local climate, but generally concentrated in April and May. Apples are cross-pollinated and most varieties do not produce fruit by themselves.</string>
    <string name="apple_cn">苹果（Malus pumila Mill.）：是落叶乔木，通常树木可高至15米，但栽培树木一般只高3-5米左右。树干呈灰褐色，树皮有一定程度的脱落。苹果树开花期是基于各地气候而定，但一般集中在4-5月份。苹果是异花授粉植物，大部分品种自花不能结成果实。</string>
    <string name="pear_en">Pear, usually variety is a deciduous tree or shrub, a few varieties for evergreen, belongs to the angiosperms dicotyledonous plant class Rose apple subfamily. The leaves are mostly oval and vary in size from species to species. The flowers are white, or slightly yellow, pink, with five petals. The shape of the fruit is round, and the base is thinner and the tail is thicker, which is commonly known as "pear-shaped"; Different varieties of peel color is very different, yellow, green, yellow with green, green with yellow, yellow, green brown, green brown, reddish-brown, brown, individual varieties also have purplish red; Wild pears have small diameters ranging from 1 to 4 cm, while cultivated varieties can be up to 8 cm in diameter and 18 cm in length.</string>
    <string name="pear_cn">梨，通常品种是一种落叶乔木或灌木，极少数品种为常绿，属于被子植物门双子叶植物纲蔷薇科苹果亚科。叶片多呈卵形，大小因品种不同而各异。花为白色，或略带黄色、粉红色，有五瓣。果实形状有圆形的，也有基部较细尾部较粗的，即俗称的“梨形”；不同品种的果皮颜色大相径庭，有黄色、绿色、黄中带绿、绿中带黄、黄褐色、绿褐色、红褐色、褐色，个别品种亦有紫红色；野生梨的果径较小，在1到4厘米之间，而人工培植的品种果径可达8厘米，长度可达18厘米。</string>
    <string name="strawberry_en">Strawberry (English scientific name: strawberry, Latin scientific name: Fragaria × Ananassa Duch.), perennial herb. 10 -- 40 cm tall, stem lower than leaves or subequal, densely spreading yellow pilose. Leaves trifid, leaflets short petiolate, thicker, obovate or rhomboid, dark green, almost glabrous above, pale pale green below, sparsely hairy, densely along veins; Petiole densely spreading yellow pilose. Cymes, inflorescence masked by a short petiolate leaflet; Flowers bisexual; Sepals ovate, slightly longer than paralsepals; Petals white, suborbicular or obovate elliptic. Aggregate fruit large, persistent sepals erect, clingy to fruit; Achene apical ovate, smooth. Flowering April - May, fruiting June - July</string>
    <string name="strawberry_cn">草莓（英文学名：strawberry、拉丁学名：Fragaria × ananassa Duch.），多年生草本植物。高10-40厘米，茎低于叶或近相等，密被开展黄色柔毛。叶三出，小叶具短柄，质地较厚，倒卵形或菱形，上面深绿色，几无毛，下面淡白绿色，疏生毛，沿脉较密；叶柄密被开展黄色柔毛。聚伞花序，花序下面具一短柄的小叶；花两性；萼片卵形，比副萼片稍长；花瓣白色，近圆形或倒卵椭圆形。聚合果大，宿存萼片直立，紧贴于果实；瘦果尖卵形，光滑。花期4-5月，果期6-7月</string>
</resources>